原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     Lynn_宁  小暴徒  吃冰棒
翻译     冬麟  Eunice  米青八刀
翻译     arcadiachi  Alex
校对     Eunice
时间轴    壬虚浪影   纸袋
后期     渔夫
总监     暴龙蛋
┌
┐
└
┘
┌
┐
└
┘
人人影视官方客户端
唯一下载渠道
app.YYeTs.com
《情事》前情提要
Previously on The Affair:
你记得第一次见她的情景吗
Do you remember the first time you saw her?
历历在目
Like it was yesterday.
我必须离开
I have to leave.
我们在一起过了半辈子
We've lived together for half our lives.
我爱上了别人
I'm in love with someone else.
我要你立刻滚出我的房子
I want you to get the fuck out of my house.
我搬到蒙托克来怎么样
What if I moved to Montauk?
为什么
Why?
跟你在一起
To be with you.
听着  我知道我是个混蛋  但是我...
Look, I know I was a jerk, but I...
我刚刚走出三年的牢狱生活
I just got out of three years in prison.
我不想像以前那样
I don't want what I used to.
我只想过简单的生活
I just want a simple life.
我只想回去教书
I just want to get back into teaching.
我想和我爱的人一起生活
I want to live with someone I love.
你是我生命中遇见的最美好的事情
You were the best thing that ever happened to me.
不  我...  我想离婚  诺亚
No, I, uh... I want a divorce, Noah.
维克怎么样了
How's Vik?
挺好的
He's good.
他刚得到一个洛杉矶的工作机会
He just got a major job offer in L.A.
在当地的儿童医院
The children's hospital there.
这个小伙子看起来挺不错的
This fella's quite a catch.
英俊  绅士  还是一位医生
Handsome, polite, a doctor.
谁都比第一任丈夫要好
Anyone would be an improvement after your first husband.
诺亚情况不太好  是吧
Noah's not doing well, huh?
他在楼下
Well, he's downstairs.
我马上就让他离开
I'll tell him to leave right now.
你爱干什么干什么  海伦
You do what you want, Helen.
因为我知道事情会发展成什么样
Because I get how this goes.
他现在走
He leaves now.
只要他一出现随便扯两句
Whenever he shows up with his bullshit,
你他妈就会立刻让他进来
you let him right back fucking in.
你为什么不直接让他走呢
Why can't you just let him go?
重点是  我这辈子
Thing is, for my whole life,
都给自己划定了界限  我是个好人
I've had this idea that I'm a good person,
这并不是真的
and, it's not true.
的确不是真的  再见
No, it's not. Good-bye.
我杀了斯科蒂·洛克哈特
I killed Scott Lockhart.
不是诺亚
It wasn't Noah.
所以我让诺亚回来
That is why I let Noah back in.
因为我觉得我欠他的
Because I felt like I owed him
我在试着弥补我做的错事
and I was trying to fix what I did.
并不是因为我爱他
It was not because I loved him.
我下班后去找你
I'll find you after work.
为人父母不是件容易的事
Being a parent is hard.
我知道我们作为父母并不完美
And I know we haven't done it perfectly,
可是我从我父母那吸取了教训
but I learned from my parents' mistakes,
你妈妈也从她父母那吸取了教训
and your mother learned from hers,
正如你也会以我们为戒
just as you'll learn from our mistakes.
直到某人  某天
Until someone someday
最终拥有一个完美的童年
finally has a perfect childhood.
我们去哪  兄弟
Where we going, buddy?
情事
第四季  第一集
已经72小时了  没人见过她
It's been 72 hours. No one's seen her.
她没有打过电话问琼妮的情况
She hasn't called to check in on Joanie.
警方已经宣告她失踪了
The police have declared her a missing person.
第一话
诺亚
六周前
我只是觉得对你来说先安定下来是很重要的
I just think it's important for you to get settled in first.
我安定下来了  海伦
I am settled, Helen.
我住的是三室的房子  我为他们每个人都准备了房间
I'm in a three-bedroom house. I got a room for each of them.
我有桌上游戏  蹦床
I got board games, trampoline.
我们是还在争抚养权吗
Are we still litigating custody here?
不  诺亚  只是
No, Noah, it's just that weekends
周末现在对他们来说真的很重要
are really important to them right now.
他们到这交了很多新朋友
They're making all sorts of new friends out here.
好  但事实仍然是
Okay, but the fact remains that
我大老远搬到洛杉矶
I moved all the way out here to Los Angeles
就是为了和我的孩子们离得近点
just to be close to my children,
可我看不到他们
and I'm not seeing them.
诺亚  我现在真的不想聊这个  好吗
Look, Noah, I really don't want to get into this right now, okay?
我们要迟到了  我得送他们上学了
We're running late, and I have to get them to school.
好  你能告诉特雷弗我今晚会去吗
Okay, will you just tell Trevor I'll be at his thing tonight?
拜托  海伦
Please. Helen
混蛋
Asshole.
康普顿学院
维克多
Victor.
你昨晚有睡觉吗
Did you get any sleep last night?
孩子每半个小时就要醒一次
The baby was up like every half hour.
信不信由你  你会怀念这个时候的
Believe it or not, you'll miss it.
是吗  你想换吗
Yeah? You want to trade?
我也没那么怀念
I don't miss it that much.
那么  有没有人能告诉我  为什么
So, come on, somebody tell me, why...
《动物庄园》
乔治·奥威尔著
为什么没有其他动物
why do none of the other animals
站出来反抗暴君拿破仑或他的喉舌  声响器
stand up to the tyrant Napoleon or his mouthpiece, Squealer?
这些猪
These pigs?
有人知道吗
Anybody?
拜托  你们是青少年
Come on. You're teenagers.
你们从没感到受压迫或是被误解吗
Don't you ever feel oppressed or misunderstood?
很好  玛蒂娜
Yes, great. Martina.
索洛维老师  我一直都想知道
So, like, Mr. Solloway, I've been wondering,
你结婚了吗
are you married?
因为我没看到你戴戒指
'Cause, like, I don't see no ring.
实际上  我离婚了  离过两次了
Actually, I'm divorced. Twice.
我喜欢有过去的男人
I like a man with a past.
好了  好了  谁想读
Okay, okay. Who'd like to read?
有人吗  有人想读吗
Somebody? Anybody?
好  玛蒂娜  你来
Yes, Martina, go on.
如果我读了  索洛维先生
If I read, Mr. Solloway,
我能当第三任吗
Can I be number three?
玛蒂娜  我对你有更高的期望
Martina, I have much loftier aspirations for you than that.
不过是的  你可以读
But yes, you can read.
第53页
Page, 53.
声响器的讲话
Squealer's speech,
从"没人相信..."开始
starting, "No one believes..."
"没人比拿破仑同志更坚信
"No one believes more firmly than Comrade Napoleon
所有的动物都是平等的"
that all animals are equal."
拜托  各位  是谁的
Come on, guys. Who is that?
能麻烦你静音吗
Can you silence it, please?
继续  玛蒂娜
Go on, Martina.
"那我们应该在哪
"And then where should we be?
假设你已决定跟随雪球
Suppose you had decided to follow Snowball,
追随他的风车梦想
with his moonshine of windmills.
雪球  据我们所知..."
Snowball, who, as we know..."
等一下  玛蒂娜  等等
Hang on, Martina. Just wait.
什么...
What...?
-给我  -不  老师  拜托
- Give that to me. - No, mister, please.
-把手机给我  -是我哥
- Give me the phone. - It's just my brother.
他放学后要送我去上班的地方
He's giving me a ride to my job after school.
我在肯德基工作
I-I work at KFC.
海米  我在教关于暴政的寓言
Jaime, I'm-I'm teaching an allegory on tyranny,
如果你不立刻把手机收起来的话
and you'll know the meaning of that
你就知道那是什么意思了
if you don't put that away right now.
-好  -现在  调成静音
- Okay. - Now, put it on silent.
好的
All right.
谢谢你  玛蒂娜
Okay, thank you, Martina.
安东
Anton.
玛蒂娜刚才读的那一段
The passage Martina just read,
声响器等于在说
where Squealer is basically saying,
"我们也想让你自己决定
"We'd love to let you make your own decisions,
可我们不能这么做  因为你的决定可能是错的"
but we can't because you might make the wrong decisions,"
能谈谈你对这句话的看法吗
you want to tell us what you make of that?
不
No.
快说吧  我们都想听
Come on. We'd all love to hear.
那很抱歉了
Sorry for y'all.
好吧  我理解  这段很难
Okay, I get it. It's a tough passage.
那  我们把这段话拆开来看
So let's, um... let's break it down.
我说了  我不想
I said I don't feel like it.
我知道你不想
I know you don't feel like it,
但我想让你参与课堂讨论  好吗
but I want you to participate in the class, okay?
所以我想让你读
So I'd like you to read it.
这样也许能加强你的理解
And you might understand it better.
来  读这一段
Come on, read the passage.
你来读
I want you to do it.
你要参与进来
You need to participate.
我没开玩笑  安东
I mean it. Anton...
我说了  不要
I said no.
威尔逊校长  有什么事吗
Principal Wilson, how can we help you?
不用管我
Don't mind me.
好吧
Okay.
那好  我们刚才读到声响器说的话
Okay, so, we were looking at, Squealer's quote.
他想表现得善良一些
Well, he's trying to come across as benign,
可他并不善良  对不对
but he isn't, is he?
他是怎样的
What is he?
没关系  这个问题很难
No problem. It's a tough question.
当我们遇到难题
When we get a tough question,
在书中总是能找到答案
we go back to the book for the answers.
海米
Jaime.
可索洛维先生说了没关系
But Mr. Solloway said it was okay.
-我没这么说过  -你说了
- No, I did not say that. - Yes, you did.
-你怎么这样  -我没说
- Come on, man. - No, I didn't.
这是我教学的方法...
No, it was a pedagogical...
就是我教学的方式...
It was a... A teaching thing. It was...
拉莫斯先生  你放学后可以来我办公室取
Mr. Ramos, you can retrieve it at the end of the day from my office.
帮帮忙  索洛维老师
Come on, Mr. Solloway.
我们不是朋友吗
I thought we were friends.
海米是想联系他哥哥
Jaime is trying to contact his brother
好让他哥哥放学后来接他
who is giving him a ride to work after school.
海米是独生子
Jaime is an only child.
没血缘关系的哥哥不行吗
Brother from another mother?
那你带着你的手机
I think you and your phone
跟我去办公室吧  走吧
can spend the rest of the day with me. Let's go.
盖特伍德先生  把兜帽摘掉
Mr. Gatewood, take down that hood.
谢谢
Thank you.
贾内尔在我的课上也是那么干的
Janelle does that to my classes, too, man.
总是半路坐进来
Always sitting in.
我可是从一开始就在这所学校任职了
And I've been at this charter since the beginning.
抱歉  我又不会了
Sorry. I'm lost again.
你想做什么
What are you trying to do?
想把测试成绩录入进去
Trying to record the grades from this quiz.
回到主页
Go back to your home page.
点那个键
Click on that tab.
然后就能进成绩录入界面了
That'll take you to your grading landing page.
谢谢
Thank you.
抱歉  我以前上课时
Sorry. We didn't really have any of this
没用过这么先进的玩意
last time I was teaching.
猜到了  你比上一个
I'll bet. You're a lot older
跟我同办公室的老师年纪大不少
than the last guy I shared this room with.
我该担心贾内尔吗
So, should I be worried about Janelle?
说实话  我觉得她在矫枉过正
To be honest, I think she's overcompensating.
因为她自己明白  雇用她是平权之举
Because she knows her hiring's an act of affirmative action.
别往心里去  我妻子说
Look, never mind. My wife says I'm not allowed
我不能再发表这样的言论了  就当你没听过
to say things like that anymore, so just, forget it.
我想问你个写作的问题
Let me ask you another writing question.
你第一篇手稿写好以后
When you finished your first manuscript,
是怎么出版的
How did you get it out there?
输入新成绩
我在读研时接触了很多人
well, you make a lot of contacts in grad school.
安东·盖特伍德  RD
乔尔  RD是什么意思
Joel, what does "RD" Mean?
意思就是他要重修该课
It means the kid's retaking the class.
预修语文不是高年级的课程吗
I thought AP English was only available to seniors.
安东·盖特伍德
Anton Gatewood?
他去年春天就该毕业了
He was supposed to graduate last spring.
可是在第二学期时抄袭
Plagiarized in the second semester,
所以贾内尔让你的前任老师挂掉了他
so Janelle made your predecessor fail him.
现在这孩子就得重修一年
Now the kid's gotta take the whole year again.
我问你个问题
So let me ask you a question.
你还有经纪人吗
Do you still have an agent?
但愿有吧
Hope so.
几个月前给他寄了份手稿
Sent him a manuscript a couple of months ago.
《东帕萨迪纳》
你看你能不能帮我...
You think there's any way you could, uh...
快点开啊
Go, go, go!
海伦
我是海伦  请留言
It's Helen. Leave a message.
是我  我这车堵住不动了
It's me. I'm completely stuck in traffic.
只有半英里的路
It says I'm a half mile away
但可能要开个四十分钟
but it's gonna take 40 fucking minutes, so just tell...
跟特雷弗说我会到的  好吗
just tell Trevor I'll be there, okay?
先生  您要去哪里
Sir. Can I ask where you're going?
抱歉  我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我儿子在这里读书
My, son is a student here.
特雷弗·索洛维
Trevor Solloway.
叫什么
Name?
我的名字吗
What, my name?
我是他爸爸  诺亚·索洛维
I'm his father, Noah Solloway.
没有
Nope.
"没有"是什么意思
"Nope"? What do you mean, "Nope"?
就是名单上没有你的名字
Nope, you're not on the list.
你有校园卡吗
Do you have a school I.D.?
我该去哪办
how do... how do I get one?
在网上
It's online, sir.
进入学校的家长必须要登记
Any parent wanting access to the grounds needs to register.
加里森先生太太  你们好
Mr. And Mrs. Garrison. How are you?
你好  请进
How's it going? Come on in.
现在来不及了  能不能给我张临时的
Okay, look, I can't do that, so can I get a temporary one?
-能用这里的卡吗  -不行
- Can I take one of these? - Nope.
我儿子在里面
Look, my son is in there.
先生  没有通行证的话你不能进去
Sir, I cannot let you through without a pass.
想象一下  如果我让你进去了
Can you imagine if I let you in
而你的前妻对你有限制令
and your ex has a restraining order out against you
今晚是她跟孩子在一起的时间
and it's her night with the kids?
你怎么知道是离婚了
How'd you know I'm divorced?
瞎猜的
Wild guess.
海伦
Helen.
接电话  海伦
Helen, pick up.
海伦  我在入口这里
Helen, I'm out... I'm at the entrance,
他不让我进去
and, um, he won't let me in.
你没有把我的名字加到名单上
You didn't put my name on the list, so, um,
你能过来给我做个担保什么的吗
can you come vouch for me or whatever?
还有...
And, uh...
请回我电话
just call me, please.
你是个混蛋  知道吗
You're an asshole. You know that?
特雷弗
Trevor.
史黛丝
Stacey.
诺亚  我没想到你能来
Noah, I didn't think you could make it.
不  我们谈过这个  海伦
No, we talked about this, Helen.
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?
你没告诉特雷弗我要来
You didn't tell Trevor I was coming?
别在孩子面前这样
Let's not do this in front of the kids.
对不起  什么样
Sorry, do what?
我们今早说好了
We talked about this this morning.
周末也说过了
We talked over the weekend.
-我已经把这个写进了日程  -好吧  抱歉
- This was in my calendar. - Okay, well, sorry.
我错了  我搞错了
I made a mistake. I got confused.
我们...  我们发生了很多事  所以
We just have... we have a lot going on, so...
不  我不是挑事
No, I'm not... I'm not making a thing of it.
只是我被卡在这了
It's just that I was stuck out here.
名单上也没有我
My name wasn't on the list.
听起来真的是个无心之过
Looks like it was an honest mistake.
我没说不是  我只是...
I'm not saying it wasn't. I'm just...
我知道  我只想让孩子们看到我来了
I know. I just wanted to show the kids that I was here.
我也确实来了
That I am here.
知道了  爸
Message received, Dad.
这样吧  一起吃晚饭
Look, come to dinner.
我们要去墨西哥餐厅
We're going to Mexican.
你也一起来
You should come.
是啊  爸爸
Yeah, Dad.
你应该一起来
You should come with us.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm late.
-爸  -你好  爸爸
- Dad. - Hi, Dad.
我坐这吗  这张椅子有人坐吗
Should I sit there? Is this taken?
谢谢
Thanks.
我把导航输成洛杉矶
I put, Los Angeles into the GPS
而不是圣塔莫尼卡  所以...
instead of Santa Monica, so...
圣塔莫尼卡和洛杉矶完全不同
Santa Monica's a whole different city.
你会熟悉的  只是需要点时间
You'll figure it out. It just takes time.
请给我一杯玛格丽塔  不加盐
Can I get a margarita, please, no salt?
谢谢
Thanks.
孩子们  猜猜我上周末都花时间装了什么
So, kids, guess what I spent last weekend setting up.
-什么  -蹦床
- What? - Trampoline.
-蹦床吗  -是啊
- Trampoline? - Yeah.
还有  我给你们的房间添了点家具
Plus, I got some furniture for your rooms,
希望你们最近可以有时间过来过夜
so hopefully you can come for a sleepover sometime soon.
我可以去玩一天
I'll come over for a day,
但我不能在那过夜
but I don't think I'm gonna sleep over.
为什么
Why not?
托潘加峡谷很吓人
Topanga Canyon's creepy.
托潘加有什么吓人的
What's creepy about Topanga?
妈妈告诉她查尔斯·曼森在那里住过
Mom told her Charles Manson lived there once.
美国著名连环杀手
是真的
He did.
你怎么知道查尔斯·曼森的
How do you even know who Charles Manson is?
我本来不知道  后来我在油管上看了他的视频
I didn't, and then I YouTubed it.
多谢了
Thanks a lot.
你呢  小特
How about you, Trev?
过夜  就你和我
Sleepover, just you and me?
他的周末行程已经满了
His weekends are kind of packed.
听听他的意见
He can speak for himself.
可以吧
Well, I mean,
我们可以商量个时间  爸爸
yeah, we can try and get something on the calendar, Dad.
好吧  那就商量个时间
Okay, something on the calendar.
妈  维克  我想跟你们谈谈驾校的事
Mom, Vik, I wanted to talk to you guys about drivers' ed.
好吧  但是
Okay, but... So--
还是再过六个月吧
maybe we'll wait six months?
不不不  我马上就15岁了
No, no, no, I'm gonna be 15 so soon, and, you know,
比别人先学是件好事
it's good to get a head start.
能把那杯玛格丽塔给我了吗
Can I get that margarita, please?
教师之夜
So, what happened...
教师之夜怎么了
what happened with teacher night?
课程之夜吗
Curriculum night?
非常非常顺利  对吗  小特
It went really, really well, right, Trev?
对
Yeah.
真的很希望那晚我去了
I really wish I had been there.
我想看你在做什么
I wanted to see what you were doing.
他就是跟我们说更多
He was just telling us more about the project
他在他们所学单元中研究的项目
he's working on in the unit they're studying.
什么项目
What's the project?
有个女孩
Yeah, so there's this girl,
住在殡仪馆里
and she lives in a funeral home.
是本书还是...
Is it a book or...
是一本漫画小说
It's a graphic novel.
那个女孩觉得她  可能是
And the girl thinks that she might be...
同性恋  不止是觉得
Gay. But not just thinks.
她就是同性恋
She is gay.
她长大后
And as she grows up,
开始发现她爸爸也是同性恋
she begins to realize that her dad was gay, too,
但没有出柜
but closeted.
你这个项目的搭档是布鲁克林吗
And your partner on this is Brooklyn?
不好意思  布鲁克林是什么
Sorry, what's Brooklyn?
是个人  还是...
Is that a... Is that a person or...
布鲁克林是个男孩
Brooklyn's a boy.
好吧  这么说布鲁克林是你的朋友
Okay, so... so Brooklyn's your friend.
我没搞懂是怎么回事
I-I don't understand what's going on.
课程之夜真的很有意思
Curriculum night was definitely interesting.
那么  在特殊单元中
And so, uh... Yeah, so, um, in the special unit,
我们会拿上我们选好的漫画小说
we then take our chosen graphic novel
研究塑造书里世界观的
and study the social issues
社会问题和历史
and history that make up its worldview.
在你这情况中  是同性恋权益吗
And in this case, it would be gay rights?
没错
Exactly.
这本漫画小说是什么
What is this graphic novel?
《开心窝》
Fun Home.
女同题材音乐剧
开心...  那不是音乐剧吗
Fun... Wasn't that a musical?
对  就是百老汇的那部
Yes, on Broadway, actually.
话说回来  真是个很酷的学习方式
Anyway, it's a really cool way to learn.
是啊  我想知道的是  小特
Yeah. Okay, what I was wondering, Trev,
我想知道  你是不是有什么
is, um... I was wondering, is there anything
想告诉我们
you're trying to express
或跟我们交流的
or communicate to us,
关于你选择的这个题材
with your choice of material?
因为我希望你知道
Because I hope that you know
我们爱你的一切  接受你的一切
we love and accept everything about you,
不管你是什么样子
whatever you are.
我知道
Yeah. I know.
你的每一部分
Every part of you.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
海伦  能借一步说话吗
Helen, can I get a word, please?
好
Sure.
不好意思
I'm sorry.
刚才那是怎么回事
What's going on out there?
他和那个男孩形影不离
He's been inseparable from this boy.
-布鲁克林吗  -对  布鲁克林
- Brooklyn? - Brooklyn, yes.
这件事我也怀疑了好久
And it's something I've suspected for a long time,
-现在终于...  -什么
- and now finally... - What...?
他是同性恋  诺亚
He's gay, Noah.
等等  所以...
Wait. So...
所以我刚才看见的是你...
So, what I was seeing out there was some kind of...
你在想办法让他承认吗
some kind of attempt to make him say that?
我真的真的希望你参加了课程之夜
I really, really wish you had been to curriculum night.
是啊  我真的努力过了
Yeah, I-I really tried.
我说不好
Look, I don't know.
在我看来这是显而易见的
It just seems to me very obvious.
你应该看看他的作品
You should see his art.
还有这个孩子  布鲁克林
And then this boy, Brooklyn.
甚至是他的...选题
And even his choice of... of material.
一目了然
It's-it's just plain as day.
好吧  首先  他才14岁  海伦
Okay, okay, first of all, he's 14, Helen.
也许...也许他在进行一些探索
Maybe... maybe he's exploring things,
不过现在还为时过早
but it's way too early
让他去承认一些...
to try to get him to confess to some--
他几乎要说出来了
Look, it was on the tip of his tongue.
不骗你  他正打算说出来的
I swear to you, he was about to say it.
真的吗  真的是这样吗
Was he? Really, was he?
还是你在诱导他
Or were you leading him?
因为我看到的是你明显在诱导他
'Cause what I saw was you were definitely leading him.
真是荒唐
This is ridiculous.
难道比你在墨西哥餐馆
More ridiculous than trying to
设法逼你儿子出柜还要荒唐吗
out your son in a Mexican restaurant,
他可能根本就不是同性恋
when he might not even be gay?
他是同性恋  不如这样吧
He is gay. And hey, guess what.
我有个想法
I have an idea:
不如你干脆承认这件事让你不舒服
Why don't you just admit you have a problem with it?
就算他是同性恋  我也没问题
I don't have a problem with it, if he is.
-他就是同性恋  -好吧
- He is. - Okay, fine.
不过  何时何地出柜
But shouldn't it still be his choice
难道不该由他自己来决定吗
as to when and where he wants to come out?
我就是这个意思
That's what I'm saying.
他正要承认  可你打断了
He was about to, until you walked in.
你让他害怕
You intimidate him.
海伦  你为什么要这么做
Helen, why are you doing this?
做什么
Doing what?
我大老远搬过来
I move all the way out here--
是的  为了和孩子们在一起
Yeah, to be with the kids, right?
我没让他害怕  也没让史黛丝害怕
I don't intimidate him or Stacey.
我只是对他们不再了解了
I just don't know them anymore.
所以我才会来
That's why I'm here.
而你在想方设法
And you're doing everything in your power
把我挡在他们的生活之外
to box me out of their lives.
知道我以后不会再做什么吗
You know what I'm not doing anymore?
这个
This.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
艾莉森  我是诺亚
Alison, it's Noah.
很抱歉这么晚了还打给你
sorry to call so late.
只是想问候一下
Just checking in.
好的  再见
Okay, bye.
麦克斯
Max,
我是诺亚
it's Noah.
信不信由你
Believe it or not.
我...
I'm, uh...
就是想问候一下
just reaching out.
希望你一切都好
Hope you're well.
再见
Bye.
斯大林主义  资本主义
乔治·奥威尔《动物农场》中的权力腐化
作者  安东·盖特伍德
安东·盖特伍德
Anton Gatewood.
周三开始  准备讲《荒原》
Beginning Wednesday, get ready for The Waste Land.
安东
Anton.
请等一下
Hold back, please.
我得去搭便车
I gotta meet my ride.
你朋友可以等一等
Your ride can wait a minute.
我想和你聊聊你的论文
I want to talk about your essay.
论文怎么了
What about it?
论文...
It's, uh...
写得非常非常非常好
it's very, very, very well done.
是吗
Is that right?
是的  你对于小说思想的分析
Yeah. Your analysis of propaganda in the novel
以及论述如何通过操控语言来...
and showing how language can be manipulated to...
行使权力  不仅仅是好
wield power, it's-it's not just good.
而是...精彩绝伦
It's... it's brilliant.
好吧
Okay.
你想说的就这些吗
So, is that what you wanted to talk about?
是的
Yeah.
真的真的很好
It's really, really good.
所以  我想知道
So, what I want to know is
论文是谁写的
who wrote it?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
就那个意思
Just what I said.
这篇精彩的论文是谁写的
Who wrote this brilliant essay?
因为我觉得不是你写的
'Cause I don't think it was you.
为什么
Why not?
证据如下
Well, let's look at the evidence.
你拒绝参与课上的内容
You refuse to participate in class.
你就坐在那里
You just sit there
头趴在桌子上  还戴着兜帽
with your head on the desk and your hoodie up.
是啊  也许是因为你讲的课太烂了
Yeah, maybe 'cause your class fucking sucks.
你我都清楚你有过抄袭的历史
We both know your history of plagiarism.
你认为你要是再被发现会落得什么下场
What do you think would happen if you got caught again?
如果我现在就带着这个直接去找威尔逊校长
If I went straight to Principal Wilson with this right now...
你觉得很好笑吗
You think that's funny?
你觉得你的前途很好笑吗
You think your future is funny?
不是的
No, man.
我觉得你很好笑
You funny to me.
为什么呢
Why is that?
好吧
Okay.
那么这句引用呢
How about this quote?
"其他动物都说声响器可以把黑的说成白的"
"The others said that Squealer could turn black into white."
好的
Okay.
给我解释解释这句话
Explain to me what that means.
在小说当中  声响器代表
So, in the novel, Squealer represents
专制国家培养的宣传机器
the propaganda machinery that despotic states develop
用来控制底层动物
in order to control their populace.
斯大林统治时期
Under Stalin,
这人是德米特里·谢皮洛夫
it was Dmitri Shepilov.
而在希特勒手下
Under Hitler,
这个人是戈培尔
it was Goebbels.
那句引用
And the quote,
"黑的说成白的"
"Turning black into white,"
就是声响器简单地说自己
is just a simplistic way of Squealer saying
能把恶行说成善举
that he can make evil sound like it was good.
奥威尔在《1984》中通过大洋国真理部
Orwell expanded on this idea in Nineteen Eighty-Four
进一步阐述了这一观点
with Oceania's Ministry of the Truth,
讽刺这个部门所做的一切都是骗人的
the irony being that all Ministry does is lie.
还有别的问题吗
Anything else?
安东
Anton.
安东  别这样
Anton, come on.
我应该向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
第二话
海伦
他们是怎么上去的
How the fuck do they stay up there?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你有什么困扰吗
Are you obsessing?
没有
No.
史黛丝  吃早餐了
Stacey, breakfast.
我要做完数学作业
I'm finishing my math homework.
你可以边吃边写
Well, you can finish it while you eat.
马上就好
Just a minute.
特雷弗  你音量能调小一点吗
Trevor, can you please turn that down?
好的  妈妈
Sure, Mom.
到底是谁在给你发短信
Who's texting you, anyway?
布鲁克林
Brooklyn.
布鲁克林  是我们之前住的那一区吗
Brooklyn, as in our former borough?
不是  妈妈
No, Mom.
布鲁克林是我的朋友
Brooklyn's my friend.
短信发个没停
Well, that's a lot of texts.
怎么  她暗恋你吗
What, does she have a crush on you?
性别错了
Wrong gender.
布鲁克林是男孩
Brooklyn's a boy.
好吧
Okay.
看
Look.
我好像减了八磅
I think I've lost like eight pounds.
或许你该停止喝青汁了
Maybe you should lay off the green juices.
你今天不是打算放松吗
Thought you were going to relax today.
我很放松
Um, I am relaxed.
-史黛丝  -马上就好
- Stacey! - Just a minute!
我说了我会送他们上学
I told you I'd get them to school.
你明明可以多睡会  去做瑜伽
You could've slept in, gone to yoga.
忙完这个我就放松
Well, I'll relax right after this.
-我保证  -宝贝
- I promise. - Babe.
-干嘛  -过来
- Yeah? - Come here.
-不要  -过来
- No. - Come here.
该死
Oh, shit.
我手上沾满了蛋黄酱
I have mayonnaise all over my fingers.
你到底在担心什么
What are you so worried about?
-弄脏你的衣服  -海伦
- Staining your clothes. - Helen.
我没在担心任何事
I'm not worried about anything.
我们有一栋超棒的房子
We have an amazing house.
只剩下两个孩子
We're down to just two kids.
他们上学很开心
They're happy at school.
我们终于都收拾好了
We're finally all unpacked.
你答应过我  我们来这里时
You promised me, when we got out here,
你会放轻松的
you'd take it easy.
我真的很放松
And I seriously am...
很快就会了
going to.
-什么时候  -今天
- When? - Today.
主治外科医生乌拉
Chief Surgeon Ullah.
再说一遍
Say that again.
主治外科医生乌拉
Chief Surgeon Ullah.
你们俩
Guys.
恶心
Gross.
真扫兴
Buzzkill.
海伦
Helen.
你还好吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
没事
Fine.
好的
Okay.
火蜥蜴们  出发咯
Sollomanders, let's rock and roll!
史黛丝  快点
Yeah, Stacey, come on.
来了
Coming.
你查出她母亲是谁了吗
Have you figured out who her mother is yet?
我觉得她有点像女星米歇尔·菲佛  你觉得呢
Think she looks a little like Michelle Pfeiffer, you think?
还好
Not really.
吉娜·戴维斯呢
Geena Davis?
你干嘛不直接问她
Why don't you just ask her?
你干嘛不问  你老盯着她看
Why don't you? You spend so much time looking at her.
不  那是你  海伦
No, that would be you, Helen.
你想她到底知不知道
Do you think she even realizes
这些垃圾箱是她的  而不是我们的
these cans are hers, not ours?
我不认为
No, I don't.
你要是继续帮她搬  她永远不会知道
And she's not going to if you keep moving 'em for her.
你好
Hey there.
早上好
Good morning.
Morning.
那些是我的吗
Are those mine?
是的  不过别担心  我弄好了
Yeah, but don't worry about it. I got it.
告诉我
So, tell me,
你今天打算做什么来放松
what are you going to do to relax today?
去做心理辅导
Go to therapy.
那只会让你讨厌你妈
That just makes you hate your mother.
我本来就讨厌我妈
I already hate my mother.
再说  这不一样  这是西岸治疗方法
And besides, this is different. It's West Coast therapy.
很放松
Very chill.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
你们准备好了吗
You guys ready?
好了
Yep.
我的余额为负数
I've got a negative balance.
抱歉  你能再说一遍吗
I'm sorry. Uh, can you say that again?
我没听见
I didn't hear you.
我说我正站在学校餐厅的结账处
I said I'm standing here in checkout at the school cafeteria,
我饭卡里的余额是负数
and I've got a negative balance on my food card.
好的  这个月轮到你父亲充钱
Um, okay, well, it-it's your father's month to pay.
你打过给他吗
Did you try to call him?
这么说你想让我挂掉电话  打给他
So you want me to hang up, try to call him,
然后等他回我电话吗
then wait around for him to call me back?
我想买好早餐去上课
I'm trying to get breakfast so I can get to class.
好的  宝贝  抱歉
Okay, sweetheart, I'm sorry.
我会处理好  给我三分钟  好吗
I'll-I'll take care of it. Give me three minutes, okay?
谢谢  妈妈
Thanks, Mom.
老天  诺亚
Oh, God, Noah.
你不是吧
I swear to fucking God.
那么
So, um,
我们试试观察你的身体
let's try scanning your body, huh?
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
观察你的身体
Scan your body.
告诉我你哪里感到压力
And tell me where you're feeling tension.
没有吗
Nothing?
我很好
I'm fine.
但今天早上
But this morning,
你以为自己感觉到地震
you thought you felt an earthquake?
没错
That's right.
很大的地震
A big one.
不如我们再观察身体一次
Why don't we try that body scan one more time?
卡普兰医生  抱歉
Dr. Kaplan, I'm sorry, I'm just really
我只是不习惯这样做治疗
not used to doing therapy this way.
在纽约我们会聊天
In New York, we-we talked.
我们不观察
We didn't scan.
你还想念纽约吗
You still miss New York?
越来越轻松了吗
Getting easier?
应该是吧
Um, yeah, I guess.
我想是的
I guess so. I guess it is.
我说不好  我就是觉得
I don't know. I just feel, um...
在这里不自在
...um, uncomfortable here.
这个城市让我感到不安全
This town, it makes me feel unsafe.
好的
Okay.
怎么个不安全法
Unsafe how?
比如  地震什么时候会发生
Well, like, for example, when's the earthquake gonna hit?
具体哪一次地震
Which particular earthquake?
大的那次  会把我们全杀死那一次
The big one. The one that's gonna kill all of us.
我们为什么
I mean, why are we all existing here
都待在这个断层线等死
on a fucking fault line just waiting to die?
你不觉得这很疯狂吗
Doesn't that seem insane to you?
好吧  我听到的是
Okay, so what I'm hearing is...
这座城市  这地方
this town, this place,
让你非常没有安全感
it really makes you feel unsafe.
对  我刚说了
Yes, I just said that.
但我现在觉得
Yes, but now I feel
我能理解你担心的级别
I understand the magnitude of your concern.
这是个地震笑话吗
Was that an earthquake joke?
不如我们再观察一次你的身体
Why don't we try scanning your body
看看是不是...
one more time just to see if we--
我觉得我儿子是同性恋
I think my son might be gay.
好吧
Oh, okay.
可能这就是你的地震
Perhaps there's your earthquake.
什么
What?
你极度惧怕的
The earthquake in your life
人生中的地震
that you so greatly fear.
这不是什么大事
I'm fine with it.
真的
I am.
我完全没有意见
I am 100% fine with it.
事实上我很高兴
I'm thrilled, actually.
我一直希望有个同性恋儿子
I always wanted a gay son.
我另外一个儿子就像加里·库珀
My other son is like Gary Cooper.
好莱坞影星
真是糟透了
It's awful.
为什么
It's awful because...?
我担心的是他的父亲
It's his father I'm worried about.
你儿子的父亲  你前夫吗
Your son's father, your ex?
对  他比较
Uh, yeah. He's not very, uh...
保守
tolerant.
我怕他会以为  这都是他的错
And I'm afraid he's gonna think it... it's his fault.
他的错
His fault?
因为特雷弗小的时候他不在他身边
For not being around when Trevor was young.
他离开了
For leaving us.
你担心你的前夫
You're afraid your ex-husband
会认为你儿子的性取向
will consider your son's sexuality
是他错误的人生选择所造成的
a result of his poor choices?
对
Yeah.
你当然知道  性取向可不是这么一回事
You know, of course, that's not how sexuality works.
我又没说我这么认为
Well, I didn't say I thought that.
我是说我担心他会这么认为
I said I was afraid he might think it.
你和诺亚之间怎么样了
Um, how are you and Noah doing?
上回  你对他来加州
Uh, last session, you were having
这件事抱有复杂的情绪
mixed feelings about his being out here at all.
很好  我们很好
It's fine. We're fine.
多见见他对孩子们有好处
Uh, it's-it's good for the kids to see him.
我对诺亚已经没有什么意见了
I don't have any problems with Noah anymore.
只是
It's just, uh... uh...
-怎么了  -他很烦人
- What? - He annoys me.
一谈到诺亚你就很不自在
You seem uncomfortable talking about Noah.
身体上的不自在
Physically uncomfortable.
你注意到了吗
Do you notice that?
海伦  请听我说
Helen, if I may.
你太过于依赖你的理智
I see you relying on your head a lot
去合理化甚至否认某些感情
to rationalize or even deny certain feelings.
你似乎没有意识到
You don't seem incredibly aware,
也没有心存感恩于这种智慧
appreciative of the intelligence,
经历
the experience,
创伤
the trauma
这些都藏在你身体里
that is hiding in your body.
什么创伤
What trauma?
你丈夫在结婚25年后
Uh, your husband left you abruptly
突然离开你
after 25 years of marriage,
然后开车撞了他新老婆的小叔
then hit his new wife's brother-in-law with a car,
逃离现场
fled the scene
最后为此坐了三年的牢
and ended up going to prison for three years.
与此同时
Meanwhile,
你的大儿子先后从两个高中退学
your older son failed out of two high schools,
差点没毕业
barely graduated,
你的女儿大学辍学
and your daughter dropped out
和年龄是她两倍
of college to run off to Paris
还虐待她的男人跑去巴黎
with a man twice her age, who abused her.
你要这么说的话
I mean, well, when you put it like that...
我来加州时就全部翻篇了
I left all of that behind me when I came to California.
我现在真没什么好担心的
I have literally nothing to worry about right now.
惠特尼已经重返校园
Whitney's back in school.
她有个和她年龄般配的男朋友
She has an age-appropriate boyfriend who she likes.
我也很喜欢他
And I like him, too.
马丁在威廉玛丽学院也很开心
And Martin seems happy at William and Mary.
小朋友们也很喜欢这里的学校
And the younger kids really like school here.
维克的工作很棒
And Vik has an amazing job.
我们住在漂亮的房子里
And we live in a gorgeous house.
而且我的父母离我十万八千里远
Oh, and my parents are 3,000 miles away.
我不想工作就不工作
I don't have to work right now if I don't want to,
每天都是大晴天  天天如此
and it's sunny every day. Every goddamn day.
都是大晴天  完美
Every goddamn day is sunny-- perfect.
但有时日晒让我觉得头疼
But you know what, sometimes the sun gives me a headache.
我还超讨厌大海
And I fucking hate this ocean.
-你讨厌太平洋  -对
- You hate the Pacific? - Yeah.
你靠它那么近时什么事都做不了
There's nothing you can do when you're around it
只能盯着它瞧
except look at it.
又大又蓝又扎眼
It's so huge and blue and obvious.
简直就是个戏精
It's like an attention whore.
太平洋是个戏精
The ocean is... is an attention whore?
你那么说  听起来我是个疯子
Okay, no, when you say it like that, it makes me sound crazy.
我不是那个意思
That's not what I was trying to--
我知道  算了  没关系
I know, but never mind. It's all right.
你理解不了的  算了
Just, you don't get it. Never mind.
我觉得这时就应该
You know, I think this would be a really good time
闭上眼睛
to just try closing your eyes
屏住呼吸
and holding your breath--
去死吧  埃泽拉
Fuck you, Ezra.
普丽娅
Priya?
我快弄完了
I'm almost done.
维克没跟我说你要来
Vik didn't tell me that you were coming over.
他跟我说他裤子总往下掉
He told me his pants are falling down,
所以我来改改
so I'm taking them in.
可以放着我来的
Well, I could have taken care of that.
你懂针线活吗
Do you know how to sew?
不懂  但我可以
No, but I could've, um...
送去别人那里
you know, dropped 'em off somewhere.
裁缝店吗
At a tailor's?
对
Yeah.
我就是个裁缝
I am a tailor.
我知道  我只是
I know. I just...
我不想麻烦你
I didn't want to bother you, so...
帮我自己的儿子有什么麻烦的
Why would it bother me to do something nice for my son?
你照顾你自己的孩子也会嫌烦吗  海伦
Does it bother you to care for your children, Helen?
你想喝点什么吗
Can I get you something?
家里有水  果汁
We have, um, water, juice.
应该也有苏打水
I think we have some club soda.
都是他爱吃的
His favorites.
印式炒茄子
Baingan bharta,
串烤鸡肉  炸脆松饼
chicken tikka, chole bhature.
我还买了印度面包  馕
I've even brought Indian bread-- naan.
在冷冻层里
It's in your freezer.
别用烤箱加热
Don't put it in the oven.
会变得脆脆的
It'll get crusty.
放进微波炉
Put it in the microwave
再用平底锅加热
and heat it in a frying pan.
他可以把吃剩的带去单位当午餐
He can take the leftovers for lunch to work.
我真不知道该说什么了
I really don't know what to say.
也够你和孩子吃了
There's plenty for you and your children, too.
你真的没必要做这些
You really didn't have to do this.
冰箱里的食物
I mean, there's enough food in there
够吃一周了
for like, a week.
我不介意每个周日都这么做
I don't mind doing it every Sunday.
-我知道你忙  -没那么忙
- I know you're busy. - Well, I'm not that busy.
我有时间烹饪
I have time to cook.
怎么
What?
维克拉姆太瘦了
Vikram is very skinny.
我知道
I know.
我觉得他压力太大了
I think he's stressed out.
新工作嘛
Um, about his new job.
也许吧
Perhaps.
也有可能他只是
Or perhaps he's simply not
不太吃得惯你烧的菜
accustomed to the food you cook.
一个丈夫应该是胖胖的才对
A husband should be fat.
这说明他很开心
It shows he's happy.
我觉得维克挺开心的  普丽娅
Oh, I think Vik's happy, Priya.
我觉得  我让他挺开心的
I mean, I... I think I make him happy.
他是这么说的
That's what he tells me.
但男人除非有了自己的孩子
Of course, no man is truly happy
否则不会真正地开心
until he has children of his own.
抱歉  我有些事要忙去了
Okay, will you excuse me? I have to do something.
-海伦吗  -是  你是谢拉对吧
- Helen? - Hi. Yes. Sierra, right?
没错  我是
Yeah, that's right.
你好吗
How's it going?
好极了  其实呢
Great, actually. I, uh...
我一早上都在摘这个
I have been picking these literally all morning,
然后发现我从来都没
and I just realized that I-I never
正式欢迎过你们  所以
really welcomed you guys, so...
谢谢
Well, thank you.
这个房间太美了
Wow, this room is great, by the way.
多谢夸奖  进来吧
Thanks. Uh, just... come in.
你的室内设计师是谁
Who's your, uh... who's your interior person?
我自己就是
Oh, I'm my interior person.
这么多牛油果
Wow, this is a lot of avocados.
对啊
Yeah. I, uh...
我自己一个人肯定吃不完
I mean, I was never gonna eat all of those on my own.
但我妈的鳄梨酱食谱简直绝了
But my mom actually has this amazing guac recipe
-她博客上有  -对了  你妈妈
- on her blog. - Oh, right, your mom.
她的博客叫什么名儿来着
What is the name of her blog again?
我回头发给你
I'll send it to you.
你皮肤好好喔
You have amazing skin.
真的
No, seriously.
我刚想跟你讲一个面膜
Like, I was just gonna tell you about this mask
可以用牛油果做的
that you can make with the avocado
真的能把你皮肤里的毒素吸出来
that, like, literally sucks the toxins out of your skin.
-但我觉得你可能做过类似的了  -没呢
- But I feel like maybe you already do something like that. - No.
-你真是容光焕发  -多谢
- No, you're glowing. - Oh. Well, thank you.
那  我走啦
Okay, well, um, I'll go.
-好  -我就想说
- Okay. - I-I did just want to say
如果你需要人陪你健身
that if you ever wanted, like, you know, a workout buddy
或者喝酒  我都经常做这些
or a drinking buddy, I do both a lot.
好极了  谢谢
Great. Thank you.
-你试过山羊瑜伽吗  -没有
- Have you ever tried Goat yoga? - Goat Yoga? No.
-就是有小山羊陪着做的瑜伽  -真的吗
- Oh, my God, it's yoga but with baby goats. - Really?
没错  它们会用小蹄子揉你
Yeah! They, like, massage you with their little hooves.
一起去做做应该会挺好玩的
So it might be fun if we wanted to do it together.
很感谢你
Well, thank you.
听上去不错  多谢了
That would be nice. Thanks.
你们搬来真是太让我开心了
I'm so glad that you guys moved in here.
真的  上一户人家真的
Really, because the last people were really...
超冷淡
cold, you know.
他们有一种死气沉沉的气场
They had a very stagnant energy.
斯堪的纳维亚人嘛
They were Scandinavian.
但是你
But you...
你的气质  怎么说呢
Your being is, like...
有一点儿
it's a little...
真的吗
It is?
我也说不好  以后会知道的
Yeah, I don't know. I-I guess we'll find out.
好啦
Okay.
再见
Bye.
学校不错啊
Nice school.
明显是的
Apparently.
没有粒子加速器  我很失望
I am disappointed there's no particle accelerator.
他们肯定会募集资金买一个的
I'm sure they'll have a... capital campaign to buy one.
也许他只是迟到了
Maybe he's just running late.
或许他找到更有趣的事做去了
Maybe he found something better to do.
你为什么还让他影响到你
Why do you still let him get to you?
我也不知道
I don't know.
特雷弗在那里
There's Trevor.
你们是特雷弗的父母吧
You're Trevor's parents, aren't you?
-我是...  -你们的儿子太棒了
- Uh, well, I'm-- - You guys have such a wonderful son.
听到没有  维克
Oh. Did you hear that, Vik?
我们有个特别棒的儿子
We have a wonderful son.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们也是这么认为的
Yeah, we really think so, too.
你们知道布鲁克林吧
And you guys, of course, know Brooklyn.
我们听说过他的一些事
Um, we know about Brooklyn
对本人不是特别了解  不过是的
more than we know him, but yes, of course.
他们简直像个连体婴
They're joined at the hip, those two.
完全难分难舍
Totally inseparable.
我希望你们了解
Which... I want you guys to know,
我们各方面都完全支持他
we totally support here in every way.
这里很包容很安全
This is a safe environment
特雷弗可以充分表达自我
in which Trevor can fully express himself.
不管怎样  很高兴见到你们
Anyway, great to see you,
也很高兴有特雷弗这样的学生
and great to have Trevor with us.
他真的很特别
He's truly special.
多谢
Thanks.
所以他是同性恋吧
So he's gay, right?
显而易见
As the day is long.
你觉得那孩子是真的独立制作了机器人
Do you think that kid made that robot by himself really,
还是说他的父母有帮忙
or did his parents help him?
这他妈怎么回事  海伦
What the fuck, Helen?
你上哪去了
No, where were you?
我不知道你他妈在玩什么把戏
I don't know what kind of sick game you're fucking playing here,
但那些也是我的孩子
but those are my kids, too,
如果你再试图把我挡在他们的生活之外
and if you ever try to box me out of their lives again--
我把你挡在他们的生活之外
Box you out of their lives?
你自己不来  这突然就成了我的错
You didn't show up, and suddenly it's my fault?
你他妈没把我的名字写到名单上
You didn't put my name on the fucking list.
什么名单  我根本不知道
What list? I don't even know--
停  够了  你们的孩子过来了
Okay, stop. That's enough. Your kids are coming, guys,
你们打算怎么做
so what do you want to do?
我们要怎么处理此事
How do we want to play this?
你是说你觉得
You're saying you actually think the producers
《开心窝》的制片人愿意让你
of Fun Home would give you the rights
导演一个学生作品
to direct a student production?
没错  我和布鲁克林
Yeah. Me and Brooklyn.
你觉得我做不了吗
You think I can't do it?
我知道你能做到
I know you can do it.
但关键是你要说服制片人
It's just a matter of your convincing the producers.
老实说  人家又不认识你
Because, really, who are you?
你只是个小毛孩
You're just some kid.
我有些好想法
I have good ideas.
所以你可以先试着说服我
So practice your pitch on me first.
这些人只给你一次机会
You only get one chance with these people.
我可以告诉你需要改进的地方
I can tell you the parts that need work.
你真的愿意帮我吗
You would do that?
你首先得和我预约时间
You have to make an appointment first.
我可是大忙人
I'm a very busy person.
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
我会让布鲁克林的妈妈给你妈打电话预约
I'll have Brooklyn's mom call your mom.
这就可以了
That'll be fine.
好
Yeah.
跟你们说  我...
You know, I, um...
我真的非常喜欢布鲁克林
I really like Brooklyn a lot.
我知道你喜欢他
Yeah, I know you do.
我为你感到高兴
And I'm really glad.
我觉得维克也为你感到高兴
And I think Vik is glad about that, too.
其实
You know...
我想和你们
if I can be honest
坦诚相待
with you guys,
有时我觉得我可能是...
sometimes I think I might be...
天呐  不好意思我迟到了
Oh, God. So sorry I'm late.
堵车真他妈糟心  天呐
This fucking traffic. Jesus.
这瓶酒给我吧  记到我们的账上
Oh, can I take that? Put that on our tab.
谢谢
Thanks.
你好  小家伙  你还好吧
Hey, little man. You okay?
你们在说些什么
What were you talking about?
没什么
Nothing.
-你好  爸  -你好
- Hi, Dad. - Hi.
我能跟你谈谈吗
Can I talk to you?
有什么事
What's going on?
马丁今天给我打电话
Martin called me today.
你忘记给他充饭卡了
You forgot to fill his food card.
这个月归我管吗
Is it my month?
-我很抱歉  -我真的很努力了
- I'm sorry. - You know, I am really trying,
但你他妈又不是世界的中心  诺亚
but you are not the center of the fucking universe, Noah.
我的天呐  海伦  别又来了
Oh, for fuck's sake, Helen, not this again.
你知道你刚刚闯入什么了吗
Do you know what you just blundered into out there
像个...像个冲进瓷器店的蛮牛一样
like a... like a bull in a china shop?
特雷弗当时准备告诉我们他是同性恋
Trevor was about to tell us he's gay.
-什么  -没错
- What? - Yes.
我...  我很肯定
I-I-I'm... I'm pretty sure
他准备告诉维克和我他觉得自己是同性恋
he was about to tell Vik and me that he thinks he's gay.
好吧
Well, okay.
好样的
Good for him.
我们替他高兴  对吧
We're happy for him, right?
没错  我们当然替他高兴
Yes, of course we're happy for him.
我就是想让他亲口告诉我们
I just wanted him to be able to tell us.
就像他刚刚要做的那样  然后你突然出现
Which he was trying to do, and then you showed up.
好吧  我当时不知情
Okay, well, I didn't know.
所以我们回去坐好  或许他会...
So let's go back out there, and maybe he'll--
不  你还看不懂刚才的情况吗
No, don't you see what happened?
你走进来  他就不说话了
You walk in, and he just shuts down.
你进来  带来怒气  满嘴脏话
And you come in, and you're angry, and you're swearing,
随手拿起啤酒  吃着薯片
and you're grabbing beers, you're eating chips and--
这可是家墨西哥餐馆
It's a Mexican restaurant.
他怕你
He is intimidated by you.
-你在胡扯  -他不敢告诉你
- That's ridiculous. - He's afraid to tell you.
如果他和我多花点时间相处
Well, maybe if he spent more time with me--
他担心你会认为这是你造成的
He's afraid you're gonna think it's your fault.
我为什么会觉得这是我的错
Why would I think it's my fault?
因为这就是你的错
Because it is.
什么  特雷弗是同性恋是我的错
What? Trevor being gay is my fault.
别说话  闭嘴
No. Shut up.
-我没这么说  -你就是这么说的
- That's not what I said. - It is what you said.
好吧  我不是这个意思
Well, it's not what I meant.
那你是什么意思  海伦
Well, what the fuck did you mean, Helen?
我...
I...
你这么想吗
Is that what you think?
如果你真的这么想
If that's what you really think,
那你对人如何成为同性恋的想法
then you've got really weird ideas
还真是别出心裁
about how people become gay.
天呐  是你
Oh, my God, it's you.
你就是地震
You're the earthquake.
我是什么
I'm the what?
你就是问题所在
You're the other fucking shoe.
你就是我永远无法放松的原因
You're the reason why I can never ever relax.
因为我每次见到你
Because every time I see you,
我就在等着下次灾难的降临
I am just waiting for the next disaster to happen.
天呐  海伦
Jesus Christ, Helen.
你这说法对我有点不公平  你不觉得吗
That's a little unfair to me, don't you think?
我不觉得
No, I don't.
数年前  这个家被你拆散
You know, years ago, you broke our family apart,
现在我在新地方总算有了新生活
and now I finally have a new life in a new place.
唯一的问题是你还牵涉其中
The only problem is you're still in it.
你想让我怎么做  海伦
Well, what do you want me to do, Helen?
不见我的孩子吗
Not see my kids?
因为那是不可能的
'Cause that's not gonna happen.
不  这我懂
No, I understand.
我...
I...
我觉得我们彼此应该尽可能的
I think we should just try to stay away from each other
保持距离
as much as possible.
好的
Okay.
再玩五分钟  已经很晚了  好吗
Five more minutes. It's pretty late, okay?
-好的  妈妈  -好的  晚安
- Okay, Mom. - Okay, good night.
晚安
Good night.
我在想或许我们该休息几天...
I was thinking maybe we could take a few days and...
去大瑟尔一趟
go up to Big Sur.
美国加利福尼亚风景区
我还没去过
I've never been there.
听说那里就像  人间天堂
It's supposed to be, like, God's country.
听着很糟糕
Huh. Sounds awful.
好啊
Yeah.
我把计划调整一下
I'll switch some things around,
来空出一个周末
try to clear a weekend.
我很想和你独处几天
I'd love to have you to myself for a few days.
我觉得我真的开始明白
You know, I think I'm actually starting to
人们为何喜欢洛杉矶了
understand why people like L.A.
你有什么看法
What do you think about that?
维克
Vik.
Vik!